SAM PROWSE

(609) 848-3748 SPROWSEART@GMAIL.COM

WEB DESIGNER & DEVELOPER UNION CITY, NJ

Hey, I'm Sam! I'm a lifelong learner who has been working in web and graphic design for the past 10 years. I love working in an environment where there's always a new problem to solve and I'm passionate about doing my best work and helping my team create great things.



EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC & WEB DESIGNER | Tabrasa, LLC October 2014 - Present

At Tabrasa, I've been responsible for managing, designing, and developing our CMS library of email and print marketing content for real estate agents and mortgage loan officers. I've also designed and built website templates, landing pages, and open house flyers for our client companies.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER | TLC Sign & Banner May 2014 - October 2014

As a junior graphic designer at TLC, I was responsible for working with customers over the phone and in person to prepare and help design their print orders. I gained valuable experience in working closely with clients to ensure their orders were completed to their specifications and shipped in a timely manner, as well as technical experience in formatting designs for print.

WEB CONTENT MANAGER | The College of New Jersey May 2013 - March 2014

As a web content manager, I was responsible for building and updating the sites for TCNJ's academic departments using Wordpress. I gained experience with HTML, CSS, Javascript, and PHP. I also designed various infographics and banners, and edited the photography used on the sites.

sprowse-dev.github.io

SKILLS

Adobe Suite

Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, Premiere, AfterEffects

Coding

HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP

Wireframes & Mockups

Figma, Sketch, Photoshop

General Skills

Email and Print Design, Mobile Responsive Email, Infographics, Illustration, Photo and Video Editing

Microsoft Suite

Powerpoint, Word, Excel, Outlook

EDUCATION

2009-2013

B.F.A Digital Art and Minor in Computer Science The College of New Jersey